http://www.schoppy.com/pages/privacy-security

Zombies
Made In The U.S.A.
Privacy Policy
Wm. Schoppy, Inc. is committed to respecting your privacy and recognizing
your need for appropriate protection and management of personal information you
share with us (the phrase "personal information" means any information by which
you can be identified, such as your name, mailing address, email address,
telephone number, etc.). The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you
what personal information we may collect from you, how we use such information,
and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to review and
correct, the information. This policy applies only to customers in the United
States.
As a part of our commitment to your privacy, Wm. Schoppy, Inc. supports and
adheres to the guidelines and practices adopted by the Direct Marketing
Association's "Privacy Promise to American Consumers." We have agreed to (1)
provide customers with notice of their ability to opt out of information rental,
sale or exchange with other marketers; (2) honor customers' requests not to
share their information with other marketers; and (3) honor customers' requests
not to receive mail, telephone or other solicitations from Wm. Schoppy, Inc.
Collecting Information About You
There may be times (such as when you purchase or order a product, subscribe
to a service, register to receive catalogs, or to participate in contests,
sweepstakes or promotions, etc.) when we ask you to provide certain information
about yourself, such as your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number,
email address, credit card information, birth date, gender, occupation, personal
interests, etc. We may also maintain a record of your product purchases.
Whether or not to provide such information is completely your own choice. But
if you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to
purchase products, or access certain services, offers and content on our web
site. In addition, we may need to contact you via phone, email or mail to
address questions or issues specific to your order, entry, etc., even if you
have opted to not receive communications from us.
In general, you can visit many of our web pages without telling us who you
are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We may track the
Internet domain address from which people visit us and analyze this data for
trends and statistics, but individual users will remain anonymous, unless you
voluntarily tell us who you are.
Using Information About
You
We use the personal information you provide for internal purposes, such as
confirming and tracking your order, subscription or registration, analyzing
trends and statistics, informing you of our new products, services and offers,
and providing you with information from and about Wm. Schoppy, Inc.. From time
to time we might establish a business relationship with other persons or
entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that
their privacy policies are consistent with ours. These are known as our Wm.
Schoppy, Inc. Partners. In such cases we might share and cross-reference
information, including personal information about you that will enable such
persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be
of interest to you.
To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online, in our
stores or through our catalogs. We may also combine that information with
publicly available information and information we receive from or
cross-reference with our Wm. Schoppy, Inc. Partners and others. We use that
combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with
us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of
interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.
We may contract with companies or persons to provide certain services
including credit card processing, shipping, data management, promotional
services, etc. We call them our Service Providers. We provide our Service
Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. We
also ask our Service Providers to confirm that their privacy practices are
consistent with ours.
Although unlikely, in certain instances we may disclose your personal
information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify,
contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing
injury to you, to Wm. Schoppy, Inc. or to others. We may also disclose your
personal information when we believe the law requires it.
Editing,
Updating, Correcting and Deleting Information About You
We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you
prefer not to receive information from Wm. Schoppy, Inc. or from the Wm.
Schoppy, Inc. Partners please let us know by calling us at 609-653-1684, or by
sending us an email. Please be sure to include your email address, mailing
address, full name, and specifically what information you do not want to
receive. If you would like to update or correct your email address, mailing
address or other personal information with us please contact us the same way.
Please note that any requests to remove or update your personal information
may take up to ten days for your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your
postal mail request.
Protecting Children
Wm. Schoppy, Inc. takes special care to protect the safety and privacy of
children. Our web sites are general audience sites. We do not permit anyone
under the age of 13 to register with us. We also do not send email
correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 13 without
their parent's consent.
Children under the age of 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for
permission before providing any personal information to anyone online. We urge
parents and guardians to participate in their children's online activities and
use parental control or other web filtering technology to supervise children's
access to the web.
Cookies
Our web sites use "cookies." A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent
to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive.
Generally, we use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our products and
services to suit your personal interests, estimate our audience size, assist our
online merchants to track visits to and sales at our sites and to process your
order, track your status in our promotions, contests and sweepstakes, and/or
analyze your visiting patterns. You can generally set your browser to not accept
cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to
decide whether or not to accept it.
We may contract with third parties who may use cookies and collect
information on our behalf. These third parties are prohibited by our contract
with them from sharing that information with anyone other than us or our Service
Providers. However, we respect your right to choose whether to be included in
such services. If you would like to opt out of these services, please contact
us.
Security
We take precautions, including use of sophisticated encryption and
authentication tools, to protect the security of your personal information that
you share with us. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the
Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to
protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security
of any information you transmit to or from our web sites, and you do so at your
own risk.
We urge you to keep your password in a safe place and not to divulge it to
anyone. Also remember to log off your account and close your browser window when
you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your
account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using
a computer in a public place such as a library or Internet cafe.
Links to Third Party Sites
Our web sites may contain links to web sites operated and maintained by third
parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked sites
may be different from our privacy policy. You access such linked sites at your
own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked site before
disclosing any personal information on such site.
Policy
Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform
you by posting a notice on our web site. Those changes will go into effect on
the date posted in the notice. The new policy will apply to all current and past
users of our web site and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent.
This policy was posted in November 2008.
Your Feedback
To help us improve our privacy policy and practice, please give us your
feedback. You may contact us at the information below.
1. SECURITY
ASSURANCE
CHOICE / OPT-OUT
Wm. Schoppy, Inc. provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. We gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
To opt-out of mailings send us an email: info@schoppy.com.
3. CORRECT / UPDATE
To correct or update any information send us an email: info@schoppy.com
CHOICE / OPT-OUT
Wm. Schoppy, Inc. provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. We gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
To opt-out of mailings send us an email: info@schoppy.com.
3. CORRECT / UPDATE
To correct or update any information send us an email: info@schoppy.com
Here's
how we protect you:
1) First, our site uses the latest in encryption technology, digital
certificates, secure commerce servers and authentication to ensure that your
personal information is secure online. Wm. Schoppy, Inc. uses digital
certificates from Verisign, Inc., a trusted third-party Certification Authority
(CA). Also known as Digital IDs, these digital certificates are similar to your
driver's license, passport or membership card in that they prove your identity.
Digital IDs are useful in electronic commerce because they verify the identity
of the parties involved. Making a credit card purchase at Wm. Schoppy, Inc. is
actually more secure than using your credit card at the local store or
restaurant.
2) Wm. Schoppy, Inc. uses 128 bit encryption for maximum security for
communications over the Internet. Furthermore, Wm. Schoppy, Inc. ensures the
privacy of the information not only online, but through our back-end systems.
2. CHOICE / OPT-OUT
Wm. Schoppy, Inc. provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving
communications from us at the point where we request information about the
visitor. We gives users the following options for removing their information
from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive
our service. To opt-out of mailings send us an email:
info@schoppy.com.
3. CORRECT /
UPDATE
To correct or update any information send us an email:
info@schoppy.com
Schoppy.com includes a 128 bit SSL certificate that is used by
the store shopping cart.
Secure Sockets Layer (SSL): How It Works
What Happens When a Browser
Encounters SSL
A browser attempts to connect to a website
secured with SSL.
The browser requests that
the web server identify itself.
The server sends the browser
a copy of its SSL Certificate.
The browser checks whether
it trusts the SSL Certificate. If so, it sends a message to the server.
The server sends back a
digitally signed acknowledgement to start an SSL encrypted session.
Encrypted data is shared between the browser
and the server.
Schoppy.com includes a PCI compliant shopping
cart and hosting for our online store.
What is PCI DSS Compliance?
The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI
DSS) is an information security standard for organizations that handle credit
card and debit card information. Defined by the Payment Card Industry Security
Standards Council, the standard was created to increase controls around credit
card data to reduce credit card fraud via its exposure. If you want to sell online and accept
payments from Visa, MasterCard, American Express or Discover credit cards, your
software and hosting needs to be PCI compliant.
There are six categories of PCI standards that must be
met in order for a merchant to be deemed compliant:
